{
    "id": "d520512ad1ed440392416e5be3adb719",
    "title": "During and while",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "20c26b5d337745a7b0427954700bcac0",
            "title": "During And While",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I read a lot of books …………………. the summer vacation.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I learned some Spanish ………………… I was working in Spain.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He arrived ………………… I was out.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "during"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She called me ………………… the lunch break.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was in hospital ……………….. the winter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "during"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will see you for a few minutes ………………. the afternoon.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I woke up several times ………………… the night.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will phone you ……………… the meeting.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I met him ………………. my stay in Canada.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I met him …………………. I was working in Canada.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "during"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}